

Claudio Pagnacco

UX/UI designer

The sum total of experiences accumulated over the years are the added value I can offer.

After a threefold career in health care, design/development, and the arts, I have gained a deep and informed view of today's world.

I pay close attention to emotional interactions, details, and new technologies as a benefit to users and companies.

Basic info

Born in Genoa, Italy on the 27th of November in 1992

Education

- Meta iOS Developer Professional certificate, Coursera (in progress)
- UX Design Master at Talent Garden, April 2023
- APR certificate, 2019
- RAC (Agents and Sales Representatives) certificate, 2018
- Hearing aid specialist 100/110 Medical University of Genoa, 2017
- · High school leaving qualification in scientific studies (PNI, physics and informatics enhancement), 2011
- ECDL core certificate, 2009

Experiences

Design & developing



- UX/UI design
- Web design
- Front-end developing
- Back-end developing

Accessibility



- Hearing aid specialist
- Accessibility comprension
- User research

Digital art



- Drone operator
- Colorist
- Video editing / filmmaking

Design & developing

2023	UX/UI designer for the project work Cicara
2014 - today	Freelance web designer and front-end developer
2021	Instagram AR filter development "Street life" reaching 3.4 billion views and 1.2 billion shares worldwide
2018	Front-end, back-end developer of amplimanager website
2014 - 2016	Web designer for Carla Lertola
2014 - 2016	Web designer for Franco Perona
2013 - 2015	Web designer for Alessandro Carnevale

Contacts



6) +39 3400733213



@claudio.pagnacco



www.claudiopagnacco.com



claudio.pagnacco@me.com

Hard skills

Team building, agile mindset, problem solving, creativity

Soft skills

UI, Interaction design, wireframing, user testing, prototyping, React, Html, CSS, Javascript, Php

Software

Figma, Miro, Slack, Adobe Suite, Visual Studio, XCode, Spark

Accessibility

2017 - 2022 Full-time hearing aid specialist at Amplifon 2011 - 2017 Part-time business procurer at Amplifon

Soft skills	Hard skills	Software
Teamwork, customer retention,business knoledge, adatability, flexibility, empathize	User research, accesibility comprension, experience mapping, user stories, acoustic physics, audio regolation, Widex, Phonak, Beltone, Oticon, Siemens	Fox, Noah, OTO Suite, Widex, Phonak, Beltone, Oticon, Siemens, Microsoft Office

Digital art

2016 - today	Freelance filmmaker and social media content strategist
2020 - today	Content creation and social management for the personal Instagram aerial landscape photography project
2020	Video assist for Rodeo Drive Srl at "Sopravvissuti" series produced by Rai Fiction, ZDF, France Télévisions
2020	Published on <u>"SOLO Fotografia Italia"</u> volume from the series dedicated to emerging photographers on the Italian scene
2016	Co-director, camera operator, editor and colorist of the docu-short film "Absence Atlas" winner of international awards
2014 - 2016	Filmmaker at DLQ Creative Factory
2014	Director and co-writer of the crowd-funding project "Primes, the trap of Riemann"
2012 - 2016	Content creator for Carla Lertola
2012 - 2016	Content creator for Franco Perona
2012 - 2016	Cover photographer for the book <u>"Liberi dalle diete"</u> by Carla Lertola edited Mondadori
2012 - 2016	Photographer for weekly column by Carla Lertola in Starbene magazine

Contacts



(o)

@claudio.pagnacco



www.claudiopagnacco.com



claudio.pagnacco@me.com

Soft skills

Team building, problem solving, creativity

Hard skills

UI, Interaction design, wireframing, prototyping, React, Html, CSS, Javascript, Php

Software

Figma, Miro, Slack, Adobe Suite, Visual Studio, XCode, Spark